It is half past nine o'clock in the morning.
Last time we were vlogs we were at another hotel.
We had a great time there, but this hotel is a paradise for children!
Yes it really is.
Now we're going to have breakfast!
Quite a little stuff.
A yogurt, a chocolate milk, and scrambled eggs and bacon.
What is the best thing about hotel breakfast?
Yoghurt!
God!
What happened there?
Yoghurt!
You just ... okay.
Harry has always loved yogurt.
Sometimes it just gets wrong.
611. 611 club, for children between 6 and 11. It goes on.
They have great fun every day!
- And we get some time ... - ... for ourselves.
- Yes.
They meet friends, they play.
It is great TUI hosts who take care of them.
You can choose whether you want the children to be there in the morning or in the afternoon.
Yes.
There are two hours in the morning, and two hours in the afternoon.
You can choose to be there both and then we would not even see our children, so we do not want that anyway.
No, exactly.
Now we are going to go the blue big water slides!
Now we will show our fantastic house!
Welcome!
Here is our very own pool!
Woho!
Alma has invited friends home several times, so we have had a pool party.
Sat on some music, offered fruit and water.
Great!
Now it is newly cleaned in here.
So nice!
Welcome in, in the small office.
Wow!
They have really made an effort!
- Mom?
- Yes?
- You know what?
- No.
- Do you want to watch a video where we test Thai candy?
- Yes!
Comment below: Yes or No.
We do as you please!
It is six o'clock and soon the sun goes down.
It is very nice to go here!
We have made ourselves in order for dinner, and I noticed that everyone has been sunbathing today.
- Yes.
- Harry.
Harry, you have red cheeks.
- What are you looking at?
- The water.
Yes, of course it is nice.
You get reassured by the beach.
Now the sun went down.
Do you hear, Alma?